export const Data1 = [
    {
      question: 'What is the process of applying to study in Australia?',
      answer: 'The process for applying to study in Australia will vary depending on the institution you choose and the program of study you are interested in. In general, you will need to apply to the institution, along with any required supporting documents, such as transcripts and proof of English language proficiency.'},
        
    {
      question: 'What is the cost of studying in Australia?',
      answer: 'The cost of studying in Australia can vary depending on several factors, such as the type, of course, you are studying, and the location of your institution. In general, you can expect to pay between AUD 20,000 and AUD 30,000 per year for tuition.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the process of applying to study  at a university or college in Australia?',
      answer: ' To apply to study at a university or college in Australia, you will need to research the institutions and programs that interest you, and then submit an application directly to the institution. You can find more information on the application process on the website.'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Do i need to have health insurance while studying in Australia?',
      answer: 'Yes, it is strongly recommended that you have health insurance while studying in Australia. This will cover you for any medical treatment you may need while in Australia.'},
        
    {
      question: 'Can i work while studying in Australia?',
      answer: 'Yes, international students in Australia are allowed to work part-time for up to 20 hours per week while studying. This can help with the cost of living and provide valuable work experience.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What are the academic requirements for studying in Australia?',
      answer: 'To study in Australia, you must meet the academic requirements for the program you want to take. This could mean that you have to have finished a certain number of courses or have gotten a certain grade point average in your previous studies. You should check with your chosen institution to determine the specific requirements.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Are there scholarships available for international students in Ausrtalia?',
      answer: ' Yes, there are many scholarships available for international students studying in Australia. These scholarships are offered by the Australian government, educational institutions, and other organizations.'
    },
    {
        question: 'What are the process for obtaining a student visa extension?',
        answer: 'To obtain a student visa extension, you will need to apply to the Australian Department of Home Affairs. You will need to provide evidence that you are still enrolled in a full-time course of study and meet the necessary health and character requirements.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Why does a visa get rejected in Ausrtalia?',
        answer: ' While the vast majority of visa applications are approved, a visa application may be rejected for a variety of different reasons, including ineligibility, a lack of evidence or documentation, character issues, health concerns, and fake documents.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Can Nepali students apply for permanentresidency in Ausrtalia after graduating?',
        answer: ' Yes, after graduating from an Australian educational institution, Nepali students may be eligible to apply for a temporary graduate visa, which allows them to work in Australia for up to four years after graduation. This can provide a pathway to permanent residency in Australia.'
      }


  ];
